http://www.yoga-in-daily-life.org/contact/legal/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
We do not collect personal information for any purpose other than mentioned in this Privacy Policy. If you choose to provide us with personal information like filling out a contact form with an e-mail address, name or postal address, and submitting it to us through the website, we use that information to respond to your message and to help you get the information you have requested.
Our website never collects information or creates individual profiles for commercial marketing or profiling. While you must provide an e-mail address for a localized response to any incoming questions or comments to us, we recommend that you do not include any other personal information.
Your e-mail address will only be used for the purpose for which you have provided it and will not be added to a mailing list. Your e-mail address will not be used for any other purpose, and will not be disclosed, without your consent.
In this regard, you should understand that you are at any time entitled to submit a subject access request (SAR), i.e. a request for personal information that the Fellowship may hold about you. You must prove that you are entitled to receive information within the framework of an SAR.  According to the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), a SAR has to be answered within 40 days of receipt of the written request. If you suspect that the Fellowship is processing your personal data in a way that is contrary to the protection of your private and personal life or violates the law, you can:
ask the Fellowship for an explanation;
demand that the Fellowship remedies the situation thus arisen.
This may, in particular, be a blocking, correction, supplementation or deleting of the personal data.
All inquiries to the Data Protection Manager (DPM) of the International Sri Deep Madhavananda Ashram Fellowship or the organization itself can be made via the e-mail address This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
You understand that in case of suspicion that your personal data are processed unlawfully, you also have the right to file a complaint with the Data Protection Authority of the Republic of Austria.
Site Visit Data
This website records your visits and logs the following information for statistical purposes: your server's IP address; the name of the top-level domain from which you access the Internet (for example, .gov, .com, .org etc.); the type of browser you use; the date and time you access the site; the pages you have accessed and the documents downloaded and the previous Internet address from which you linked directly to the site.
We will not identify users or their browsing activities, and will not disclose the information to third parties, except when a law enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect the service provider's logs.
We use buttons from Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter and YouTube on our websites. The program code of these buttons allows these companies to collect personal information of our website visitors even if they are not logged in to these services. We also use facebook pixelcode to track actions and events on our website. For more information read the privacy policy of these social media service provider.
Cookies
A cookie is a small piece of software code (text) that an internet website sends to your browser when you access information at that site. A cookie file will be saved on the local hard drive and is neither a virus nor a spyware. It helps the website to remember information about your visit, like your preferred language and other settings. That can make your next visit easier and the site more useful to you. Cookies play an important role. Without them, using the web would be a much more complicated.
This site uses the following kind of cookies: session cookie and permanent cookie. Within your browser possibilities, you can either inspect, delete or block our cookies. Be aware that disabling cookies will affect the functionality of this and many other websites that you visit.
For more general information on cookies see the Wikipedia article on HTTP Cookies.
Google Analytics and Fonts
This site uses Google Analytics which is one of the most widespread and trusted analytics solution on the web for helping us to understand how you use the site and ways that we can improve your experience. For more information on Google Analytics cookies, see the official Google Analytics page.
Third party analytics are used to track and measure usage of this site so that we can continue to produce engaging content. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site or pages you visit which helps us to understand how we can improve the site for you.
Our website uses free Google fonts. To render the fonts correctly, your browser connects to Google servers in the background. The use of Google fonts is not authenticated and Cookies are not sent by website visitors to the Google Fonts API. In the background, however, requests are made to resource-specific domains such as fonts.googleapis.com or fonts.gstatic.com. These requirements of your Web browser for fonts are separate from and do not include any credentials that you send to google.com while using other Google services like Gmail. However, the Google servers may see your IP address. Therefore, you agree to the process described above to continue to use our website.
Hyperlinking
This website may contain links to other Internet sites on the World Wide Web. The Yoga in Daily Life® ePresence provides such links for your convenience only and is not responsible for the content of any website linked to or from this site.
Links from this site to any other website do not mean that the Fellowship approves, endorses or recommends that website. The Fellowship disclaims all warranties, express or implied, as to the accuracy, legality, reliability, or validity of any content on any other website.
When you select a link to an outside website, you are leaving the policies of our website and are subject to the privacy and security policies of the owners of the outside website. The Yoga in Daily Life® ePresence is not responsible for the contents and reliability of the linked websites and does not necessarily endorse the views expressed in them. We also cannot guarantee that these links will work all the time and we have no control over the availability of linked pages.
Security
Our internal data protection policy defines how we deal with data and what information technology means our data can be processed and how the systems used to comply with current security requirements. We have taken extensive technical and operational precautions in order to protect personal data from unauthorized access and misuse. Our security procedures are monitored regularly and updated in line with technological progress.
Event Participation
All our yoga events (seminars, workshops, travel etc.) are organized in various countries as a continuous series of events and are dedicated to personal health, spiritual as well as personal development.
By registering for any yoga event, you explicitly agree - with your sign to the application - to the processing of your personal data. You understand, that the processing of these takes place in accordance with the EU GDPR law. You read and understand the further information of this Privacy Policy that you have taken note of and you know about your right to information.
This personal data is collected only to organize the event and because the state authorities in the event countries require extensive data. The personal data will not be used for advertising purposes or passed on to unauthorized institutions.
Information on the Personal Data Processing
The personal data subject (i.e. the event participant) acknowledges that the national Yoga in Daily Life® associations and the International Sri Deep Madhavananda Ashram Fellowship (hereinafter referred to as 'the Associations'), as the data controllers and as the data processors, are authorized to process subject personal data stated in the application (e.g. first name, surname, address, telephone, email, etc.) for the purpose of fulfilling the Associations´ contractual obligations arising from the subject’s participation in the ongoing series of yoga events.
The personal data subject acknowledge that the Associations are - to the extent necessary and for as long as necessary for the given purpose of processing - authorized to process their personal data necessary for the fulfillment of legal obligations arising for the Associations from the valid accounting and tax legislation, and also if this is necessary for the protection of rights and legitimate interests of the Associations.
In this regard, every participant of such events can at any time ask the Associations for access to their own subject personal data. If the Associations or the processor processes the personal data in a way that would conflict with the protection of the private and personal life, or contravene the law, the personal data subject can ask the Associations or the processor for an explanation and demand, that the Associations or the processor remedy the situation thus arisen. This can, in particular, involve blocking, making a correction, supplementing or deleting the subject’s personal data.
The personal data subject understands and explicitly agrees, that in the course of the event the Associations can make official promotional recordings, photos and videos in which the subject may appear. The subject further agrees with their publication on social media and Yoga in Daily Life® websites. After the event, these posts may be shared in private social media. The subject understands, that they may revoke their consent of itself at any time with the exception of printed media. In case the subject does not agree with the appearance in official recordings, photos and videos made at the event, it will notify the Associations´ staff of this fact prior to the commencement of making recordings or photos, and the subject will comply with their instructions to take a position separate from the place where recordings and photos will be made.
Newsletter Subscription
This service enables you to subscribe yourself to one or more of our newsletters. Therefore, if you wish to receive our newsletters, a registration is mandatory, in which context you have to state some of your own personal data (name, e-mail address).
Your personal data stated during the registration is stored and used for the carrying out of the subscription to the newsletter. You may cancel any newsletter you are subscribed to at any time by using a cancellation link at the end of the respective newsletter.
We will not transmit your personal data to any third parties without your explicit consent.
Policy Status
We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time according to the applicable law. The current status is May 2018.
Last updated on 26 May 2018.
Copyright © 1998-2020 Yoga in Daily Life. All Rights Reserved.
